Robert Hillyer Papers
Robert Hillyer Papers
- Miscellaneous
  - Tearsheets of review of The Gates of the Compass (Box 16)
  - Tearsheets of reviews of Riverhead (Box 16)
  - Tearsheets of reviews of Pattern of a Day (Box 16)
  - Tearsheets of reviews of My Heart for Hostage (Box 16)
  - Tearsheets of reviews of Poems for Music (Box 16)
  - Tearsheets of reviews of The Death of Captain Nemo (Box 16)
  - Tearsheets of reviews of The Suburb By the Sea (Box 16)
  - Tearsheets of reviews of The Relic and Other Poems (Box 16)
  - Tearsheets of reviews of In Pursuit of Poetry (Box 16)
  - Tearsheets of reviews of Collected Poems (Box 16)
  - Clipping on The Lyric Award (Box 16)
  - Clippings mentioning Hillyer (Box 17)
  - Obituaries and commentary on death of Hillyer (Box 17)
  - Clippings about Harvard (Box 17)
  - Miscellaneous clippings (Box 17)
  - Copy of The New Republic containing Hillyer's first poem (Box 17)
  - Magazines containing articles by Hillyer (Box 17)
  - Guest book from Pomfret (Box 17)
  - Ship's log and guest book (Box 17)
  - Photographs (Box 18)
    Photographs of Robert S. Hillyer, his family, relatives, friends, and acquaintances. Taken in various places, the photos are in black and white and several sizes
  - Manuscripts consist of miscellaneous manuscripts by members of Hillyer's family (Box 18)
  - Manuscript consists of Claude Raines' notes for Speech at Hillyer Farewell Dinner at Harvard (Box 18)
  - Program of Memorial Service for Hillyer (Box 18)
  - Memorial issue of University of Delaware Literature Magazine Venture (Box 18)
  - School Reports of Stanley Hillyer (Box 19)
  - Papers pertaining to the publication of In Pursuit of Poetry (Box 19)
  - Robert Hillyer's address book; and appointment books for 1950-1956 and 1960 (Box 19)
  - Manuscripts of literary writings other than Hillyer's (Box 19)
  - Manuscripts of literary criticism or essays not written by Hillyer (Box 19)
  - Various programs of literary events (Box 19)